{
    "questions": [
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(1188 \\bmod 2 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(1748391 \\bmod 2 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(39393 \\bmod 2 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(44 \\bmod 2 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(1180 \\bmod 5 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(1748391 \\bmod 5 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(39395 \\bmod 5 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(44 \\bmod 5 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(1188 \\bmod 10 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(1748390 \\bmod 10 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(39390 \\bmod 10 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(44 \\bmod 10 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(1188 \\bmod 3 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(1748391 \\bmod 3 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(39391 \\bmod 3 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "\\(44 \\bmod 3 = 0\\)",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "preamble": "8e62b2b0-9b06-48d2-94a1-641ed031858c",
            "question": "What is the sign of the answer?",
            "answer": "2",
            "choices": [
                "Negative",
                "Zero",
                "Positive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "preamble": "8e62b2b0-9b06-48d2-94a1-641ed031858c",
            "question": "What is the magnitude of the answer compared to that of \\(\\frac{5}{6}\\)?",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "Less than \\(\\frac{5}{6}\\)",
                "Equal to \\(\\frac{5}{6}\\)",
                "Greater than \\(\\frac{5}{6}\\)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "preamble": "83f9c8f5-f044-46e2-9fff-fe21cbabeb75",
            "question": "What is the sign of the answer?",
            "answer": "0",
            "choices": [
                "Negative",
                "Zero",
                "Positive"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "mcq",
            "preamble": "83f9c8f5-f044-46e2-9fff-fe21cbabeb75",
            "question": "What is the magnitude of the answer?",
            "answer": "1",
            "choices": [
                "\\(\\frac{5}{6} - \\frac{8}{3}\\)",
                "\\(\\frac{8}{3} - \\frac{5}{6}\\)",
                "\\(\\frac{5}{6} + \\frac{8}{3}\\)"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "preambles": {
        "8e62b2b0-9b06-48d2-94a1-641ed031858c": "\\(\\frac{5}{6} \\times \\frac{8}{3}\\)",
        "83f9c8f5-f044-46e2-9fff-fe21cbabeb75": "\\(\\frac{5}{6} - \\frac{8}{3}\\)"
    }  
}
